# ason **Hannanto**

3001 Front St. Alhambra, CA 91803

🛘 (626) 267-6038 | 💆 hannanto@usc.edu | 🦂 www.JasonHannanto.github.io | 🖸 JasonHannanto | 🛅 JasonHannanto

# Summary\_

Hi! My name is Jason. I'm currently a sophomore at the University of Southern California pursuing a B.S in Computer Science. Creating and perfecting a smooth and exciting user experience on a digital platform is my craft and I'm always excited to learn about new methods and technologies to better develop solutions.

#### Education

#### **University Of Southern California**

Los Angeles, CA

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE, COMPUTER SCIENCE

Expected Graduation: 2020

# **Work Experience**

#### **USC Davis School of Gerontology**

Los Angeles, CA

WEBMASTER

Aug 2017 - Present • Development and Maintenance of online websites and courses.

· Stack: HTML, CSS, Wordpress, Blackboard

#### **Reliant Pulmonary/Critical Care**

Monterey Park, CA

MEDICAL SCRIBE

Mar. 2016 - Aug 2017

- Complete realtime/retrospective charting of patient encounters, including History of Present Illness, Review of Systems, Past Medical History, Family/Social History, Assessment (ICD-10 coding)/Plan, Vitals, Diagnostic Tests, and Medications.
- Navigation/set-up of EHR/Radiographic Imaging software/programs
- Documentation/Transcription of Lab Results, Radiographic Imagery Reports, and procedural reports.

# **Projects**

#### [Current] Music Lyric/Chord Management Web App

WEB APP ALLOWS USERS TO CREATE/STORE SONGS WITH CHORDS FOR LIVE PLAYING. FEATURES THE CAPABILITY TO TRANSPOSE

Aug 2017 - Present

- KEYS LIVE. USED WEEKLY BY THE CHURCH MUSIC TEAM. · Working under a Senior Software Developer
- Debug posted issues / Refactor code for efficiency
- · Develop new features for Web App

#### [Current] JasonHannanto.github.io

PORTFOLIO WEBSITE Aug 2017 - Present

· Creating a visually appealing and responsive website

### Affiliation\_

#### **Scope USC**

GENERAL MEMBER September 2017 - Present

- · Scope is USC's Computer Science club where the top students come together to build, create, and learn new technologies and projects.
- · Current Project: React Native

## Skills\_

**Programming** C++, Python

**Frontend** HTML, CSS, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap

**Backend** Node.js, Express.js Database NoSQL, MongoDB

Version Control Git

Paradigms REST, OPP, Unit Testing